http://www.zodshopdesign.co.uk/privacy-policy/

Photography
This Privacy Policy is designed to assist you in understanding how we collect and use the personal information you provide us.
What information do I collect?
When you visit zodshopdesign.co.uk you may provide us with two types of information: personal information you knowingly choose to disclose that is collected on an individual basis and website use information collected on an aggregate basis as you and others browse this website.
Email Information
If you choose to correspond with us through email, we may retain the content of your email messages together with your email address and our response.
Web Site Use Information
Each time someone accesses zodshopdesign.co.uk the server records technical information about that person’s operating system, browser type and version, screen resolution, time taken on each page etc. No personal information is collected by this process. This information is analysed in order to improve this website.
How do we use the information that you provide?
We use personal information for the purposes only of administering this website.
Use of Cookies
zodshopdesign.co.uk uses the technology known as cookies. A cookie is a small piece of data which is sent from a web server to a web browser and stored locally on the user’s machine. The cookie is not an executable program and cannot do anything to the machine. The data may be used by that web site only, to track your choices and information such as passwords and lists of pages visited. A user can disable the us of cookies on their machine.
Sharing information with third parties
We never share e-mail or other information with third parties. Ever.
